

## **PROFILE**

I am a Junior Frontend Developer with about one year of experience. I am skills in this field, dedicating 6-8 hours a day to it.

I have experience in web application development, currently focusing on React, also have basic knowledge in website

## **SKILLS**

- Redux / RTK
- Type Script
- Java Script
- HTML5
- CSS3

- SASS
- Tailwind

- Gulp

## LANGUAGES

- Polish B2
- Russian native
- Ukrainian native

# SVETLANA MOISEIENKO

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

### WORK EXPERIENCE

## Junior Front-end developer Malevich / Sept 2022 - Dec 2022)

· Developed corporate websites in React to train and develop new employees in a "pass the game" format, in development team.

## Front-ent developer | Part time FotoDom / July 2022 - Aug 2022)

 Designed and developed a small promotional website for the company using Bootstrap as a base.

#### Internship

Pago HR / May 2022 - June 2022

• Developed a website for a charity and also managed social media.

## **EDUCATIONAL HISTORY**

#### Udemy

July 2022 - Aug 2022

#### Fundamental JavaScript. With practice and projects

- Learned basic Java Script practices
- · Mastered the basics of OOP
- Put the knowledge into practice in training projects

#### Нетология

Nov 2021 - Dec 2021

#### **Fundamentals of Figma** First steps in JavaScript

 Started to learn frontend and dive into the IT field

#### **Wroclaw Business Academy**

- · Specialisation: management
- GPA: 4.6



